{
    "subject": "resource/The_Devil's_Own",
    "predicate": "property/screenplay",
    "object": "* David Aaron Cohen\n*",
    "human_readable": "The screenplay of The Devil's Own was written by David Aaron Cohen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9429212212562561,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for The Devil's Own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8943855166435242,
            "question": "Is David Aaron Cohen known for writing screenplays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8621823787689209,
            "question": "What kind of work did David Aaron Cohen do for The Devil's Own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8031257390975952,
            "question": "What is the name of the film with a screenplay by David Aaron Cohen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7805630564689636,
            "question": "What are some common themes in screenplays written by David Aaron Cohen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6949841976165771,
            "question": "What research might have been involved in writing the screenplay for The Devil's Own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6274393200874329,
            "question": "What challenges might David Aaron Cohen have faced while writing the screenplay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295244455337524,
            "question": "Can you name any other films written by David Aaron Cohen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5195567607879639,
            "question": "How did the screenplay of The Devil's Own contribute to the success of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2701757550239563,
            "question": "What genre is The Devil's Own likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The screenplay of The Devil's Own was written by David Aaron Cohen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4516_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the screenplay of The Devil's Own contribute to the success of the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4516_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other films written by David Aaron Cohen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4516_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What challenges might David Aaron Cohen have faced while writing the screenplay?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4516_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4516_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is my answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while David Aaron Cohen is mentioned in several documents as a screenwriter, he is only credited as one of the writers of The Devil's Own in document 44 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4516/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt). However, the other documents mention that the screenplay was written by Kevin Jarre, David Aaron Cohen & Vincent Patrick, with no clear indication of who wrote the final version."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents state that \"The Devil\u2019s Own\" (1997) was \"written by David Aaron Cohen, Vincent Patrick, and Kevin Jarre\". This supports the query that the screenplay of \"The Devil's Own\" was written by David Aaron Cohen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The screenplay of The Devil's Own was written by David Aaron Cohen, Vincent Patrick, Kevin Jarre, and Robert Mark Kamen, not just David Aaron Cohen.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}